{
    "id": "dbda2f30daac48f08f27ff64b5998fcf",
    "title": "Coordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d46fce8652d54cbaa0348b9bad5cb7d0",
            "title": "Coordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is …………………………… intelligent ……………………….. hard working.",
                    "description": "Either could be used here with totally different meanings. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither, nor",
                        "both, and",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They need ……………………………. food ………………………… shelter.",
                    "description": "The correct options are both...and... and not only...but also....",
                    "answers": [
                        "both, and",
                        "not only, but also",
                        "not only, as well as",
                        "both, as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She works hard ………………………….. she is struggling to make ends meet.",
                    "description": "Yet is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "so",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I want ……………………….. this ………………………. that",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "either, or",
                        "neither, nor",
                        "both, as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He got up …………………………… rushed towards the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "then",
                        "and"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I tried my best ………………………… I could not solve the puzzle.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "but",
                        "yet",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was the most deserving candidate …………………………… she got the job.",
                    "description": "And is not wrong here. So is more correct.",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "so",
                        "so that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t like cricket, ………………………… does my husband.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "and",
                        "nor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not a man …………………………. a boy was spared.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "nor",
                        "and",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She seemed ……………………….. surprised …………………………. worried.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "both, as well",
                        "neither, nor",
                        "neither, or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ………………………….  a rogue or a lunatic.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither",
                        "either",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They will win ................................... they are well trained.",
                    "description": "For can mean because in a formal or literary style.",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}